<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Thomas Coudrat</title>
 <link href="http://thomas-coudrat.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://thomas-coudrat.github.io/"/>
 <updated>2015-03-03T20:35:17+11:00</updated>
 <id>http://thomas-coudrat.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>Thomas Coudrat</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>My hello world post, thanks to ResBaz</title>
   <link href="http://thomas-coudrat.github.io/2014/02/18/helloWorld/"/>
   <updated>2014-02-18T00:00:00+11:00</updated>
   <id>http://thomas-coudrat.github.io/2014/02/18/helloWorld</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am currently attending the &lt;a href=&quot;http://melbourne.resbaz.edu.au/conference&quot;&gt;ResBaz conference&lt;/a&gt;
in Melbourne, a great initiative that brings together multidisciplinary researchers who have a
common goal of learning about and sharing their knowledge of digital tools. I
have been helping out with Python programming, and am currently improving my
knowledge of Git.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the tool centric format of this conference, I found myself sharing
information about our favourite tools more easily. That was further
facilitated by a &amp;quot;research tools&amp;quot; poster session, all attendees were asked to
fill out a poster template that focusses on what they use, and what they do
with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been wanting to start a simple website for a while, in order to have a
landing page that I control, and possibly to have a medium where I can share
research related write-ups. And thanks to #ResBaz, it has finally happened! I
was looking the tool poster from @cammerschooner, and he had a github.io
webpage (a web hosting solution I wanted to try). I found him at the conference
and within the day I had my first website running!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used the Poole/Hyde template, and have started making changes to it: the
look of the website now may very well change quite a bit as I understand a bit
more about CSS syntax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I must thank @cammerschooner for his kind help, and the ResBaz conference for
making this happen!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
